We are back!
我們回來啦!
Let's go!
我們走
Nuts!
糟糕!
Gimme the Black Beauty.
再給我一把,黑男孩.
Alvin, take it easy up there. You've got to share the spotlight.
Alvin, 放鬆點. 你是全場焦點.
You got it, Dave.
知道的, Dave.
- Dave. - I'm serious, Alvin. This is a charity benefit.
- Dave. - 我是認真的, Alvin. 這個是有關慈善的.
- It's not all about you. - Sorry,Dave. I can't hear you ...
- 這不僅僅是你自己. - Dave，我聽不到你說什麼 ...
over the thousands of fans screaming my name.
很多歌迷在喊我的名字.
I've got  this.
我知道.
I need a help, boys.
幫我一把.
Alvin, will you please get down from there.
Alvin 你趕緊從那裡下來.
I can't hear you.
我聽不到你說什麼.
- Alvin, I'm not kidding. - What?
- Alvin,我不是開玩笑的. - 什麼？
- Dave, look out! - Alviiiiiiiiinnn!!!
- Dave 小心! - Alviiiiiiiiinnn!!!
Oh, Dave. Dave?
Oh, Dave. Dave?
This should help with the pain.
這可以減輕疼痛
I wannna talk to my boys.
我想和孩子們說說話.
I just gave you a sedative that will take effect in about one minute, so...
我剛剛給你打的鎮靜劑將在一分鐘後起效，所以...
But, let them in, quickly.
讓它們進來，快點
- Dave! - You are alive! - Hey guys!
- Dave! - 嘿，夥計，你還活著
- It was an accident. I swear. - Are you OK?
-.那是一個意外，我發誓 -你還好嗎
- I'm really sorry, Dave. - I'll be fine.
-真抱歉，Dave - .我還好
I'm just gonna be stucked here for a while.
我只是還要呆在這裡一段時間
And until I get out, I made arrangements for my aunt Jackie to come and stay with you.
在我離開這裡之前 我會安排Jackie阿姨和你們呆在一起
Who is Aunt Jackie?
誰是Jackie阿姨
The one who sent us those mail package of  yummy popcorn for Christmas.
就是在聖誕節給我們郵遞美味的爆米花那個
- Popcorn Jackie. - You don't have much time Mr Seville.
- 爆米花Jackie - Seville先生，你沒有多少時間了
Listen, I want you guys to go home and live a normal childhood.
聽著， 我想你們都回家去過像正常孩子的生活
I even made arrangement  for you to go to school.
我甚至已經安排了你們上學的事宜
- School? - Yes, school.
- 上學？ - 是的，上學
Simon, I'm putting you in charge.
Simon,我全部托付給你了
- You are? - I'm counting on you.
- 你？ -我指望你了
Dave, wait a minute.  Why is he in charge?
Dave，等一下 為什麼要交付給他？
- He's counting on me. - Dave, please, don't die.
他指望我了 - Dave,求你了，別死啊
He just sleeping. He had a sedative.
他只是睡覺 他剛剛打了鎮定劑
Ah, a sedative.
噢，鎮定劑
Excuse me, I'm here to escort the Chipmunks home.
打擾了， 我來這裡是來護送花鼠們回家的
We are not leaving Dave. I'm putting my paw down on this one.
我們不離開Dave 我就呆在這裡了
You come here.
你過來
I got it! I'll fix it! No, made it worse.
.我知道了，我會搞掂！那會更加糟糕
Please, please go.
求你了，走吧
More stress you put on persistent the longer will take him to recover.
你越是堅持 他就越好不了
You are too slow, nanny.
你太慢了，姥姥
You'll never hit me! I'm not going anywhere without Daaa... ...aaaydream believer, and a homecoming queen...
你阻止不了我的，沒有Dave我哪裡也不去 夢信徒，和歸國皇后...
I hope for your sake he stays asleep for the entire flight.
我希望為了你他能在整個飛行途中都不會醒來
Maybe you should give him another shot. Just to be sure.
也許你應該再給他打一針，以防萬一
Any ideas on how we gonna find aunt Jackie?
有什麼主意讓我們找到Jackie？
Follow me.
跟我來
Excuse me. Sorry.
讓一下
- Look, aunt Jackie! Aunt Jackie! - Popcorn Jackie.
看，Jackie，Jackie 爆米花Jackie
- Oh, come on dears. - Yeah, we got you.
過來，親愛的 我們找到你了
- Popcorn! - Who's sending to Theodore's?
- !爆米花 -誰去送給Theodore
Oh, there is a plenty for everyone. Give a hug first.
每個人都有份 給我一個擁抱先
Come over here, you old teddy bear.
過來這裡，你這個老泰迪熊
I'm not really much of a hugger.
我不是那麼喜歡擁抱
Oh, boys, I want you to meet someone. This is my grandson Toby. Toby?
孩子們，我介紹個人你們認識 這是我的孫子Toby，Toby？
Hi, I'm Theodore.
嗨，我是Theodore.
- Toby?! - What, what happened?
- Toby? - 怎麼了？
- The boys! - Oh, hey! Hey,how are you? I'm Toby. Nice to meet you.
- 孩子們 - .噢 嘿 你好我是托比，很高興見到你
Toby is living with me 'til he figures out what he want to do with his life.
托比現在和我住在一起 直到他想到他以後要怎麼辦
So far that means going beeoo-beeoo-beeoo with his thumbs the all day.
現在看來就成天用他的大拇指 嗶嗶嗶
For the record goin' beeoo-beeoo-beeoo with my thumbs right now is keeping me in first place, and that's important.
.重要的是我的手指嗶-嗶-嗶 一直保持第一名
- Toby get the bags. - What bags?
- .Toby拿上包 - 什麼包？
- The lighters. Get the luggages. - Oh, the lug, right. Let me get those...
- 拿行李 ..噢 行李 對了 讓我把那些也帶上....
- Toby! - Get the brake! Get the brake!
- Toby! -快剎車，快剎車
I'm fine.Don't worry!
我很好，不用擔心
I'm so sorry, aunt Jackie. I'm so sorry. Is she goin' to be ok?
真抱歉，Jackie阿姨 她還好嗎？
Don't worry about me, I will be home with no time.
別擔心我，我會很快回去的
I wouldn't be so sure.
我可是不那麼肯定
It was an accident, I swear.
那是一個意外，我發誓
Been there, done that. Several times.
在那裡 好幾次這樣了
I guess he will be taking care of us now?
我在想他現在會照顧我們嗎?
I'll take frankly foster of five hundred please-outs.
我坦率的說他肯定會讓我們離開的
Ain't no problem. I can totally do this.
別擔心，我完全能做好
I mean, I took care of my cat...  until it ran away.
我是說，我以前把我的貓照顧得很好，直到它跑了
Well, 'ran away' is kind of strong wordin', I think he just wanted his space.
「逃跑」也許是說難聽了點 我想是它想有自己的空間吧
I still see him around neighbourhood.
但我還在附近看到過它
You know, he like hisses and claws at me. but I think that's his way of saying we're still tight, you know.
你知道嗎，它喜歡用爪子抓我， 這說明我們還是很親密的
You guys are nothing to worry about, seriously. 'Cause, I'm not gonna be like Dave, you know, Dave is gone.
你們真不用擔心這個 我不會和Dave一樣的，你們知道，Dave已經離開了
Gone?
不在了？
Not gone, not gone gone. He is not dead. He's very much alive.
不是不在了， 他還沒有死，他還活著呢
He completely coming back. I'm just gonna be in his room, keepin' his bed warm.
他肯定還會回來的 我要把他的房子弄得很溫暖等他回來
I'll be doin'my thing,you'll be doin' your thing. I mean, you don't need to know that I'm there.
你做你的事我做我的事 我意思是說你可以當我不存在的
We supposed to know that you there, that's the whole idea.
可我們知道你在這兒 這才是關鍵
Yeah, ok absolutely. You know that I'm there,I'm just... I'm not gonna be like: I know everything, and you do this, and you do that.
是的，你們知道我在，我只是.... 我不會像這樣：我什麼都懂，你去做這些，你去做那些
I mean that.
真的
All right, let's do this.
好的 那就這樣吧
Oh, boy!
夥計
Theodore, we gonna be just fine.
Theodore我們會很好的
The important thing is...we're all still alive.
重要的是我們還活著
Well, maybe my "Get Well" card will  help Dave to come faster.
也許做一張 「康復「卡片會讓Dave快點好起來
It needs just a touch more glitter.
我們拿多點閃粉
That should do it. Who's hungry?
那很好 誰餓了？
- Uh, uh me, me! - Let's eat.
我，我 .我們吃東西吧
Nada. Find anything?
Nada，找到什麼了嗎
It's a food ghost town in here. Alvin?
Alvin?這裡是美食城嗎？
Bingo. Dinner, she is  aserved.
晚餐，來了
Hey, what are you doing in here?
嘿，你在幹什麼？
A cheese ball?
奶酪球？
Thumb boy, give me a second, real quick.
給我點時間，很快
Alvin, I really need to focus, right now because I'm one knockout away from my heavy weight title.
我現在真的需要集中精神了 我的重量級冠軍已經近在咫尺了
Can we play as well?
我們也能玩嗎？
You know, I don't want to  hurt your feelings, but else you don't want see anyone get hurt and there gonna be fistsufferean flyin'.
你知道，我不想傷害你 你也不想看到任何一個受傷是吧
We can play monopoly.
我們來玩MONOPOLY吧
We play monopoly with Dave all the time.
我們成天都和Dave玩這個
That sounds funny. We should do that sometime right.
聽起來不錯 我們也應該這樣
Now, I got to back and floatin' like a butterfly and stinging like the bee.
.現在，我要回去像蝴蝶蜜蜂一樣勤勞工作啦
Who needs Toby, Theodore, you got us.
.我們不需要Toby，Theodore 你有我們了
Yeah, who needs Toby? Boys, right this way.
是啊，誰需要Toby。夥計們，這邊
I'm gonna puke.
我想吐
Do you know what Dave would say if he were here right now?
如果Dave在這裡的話他會怎麼說呢？
But I think it means to come more from the belly.
我想一定氣到他
Get together. Be cool.
過來 別吵
- Helllooooo? - Boys, it's me.
大家好 夥計們，是我
Dave?
Dave?
Well, I guess since you've answered the phone,  you haven't burned down the house yet.
我想你接了電話後 應該還沒有把房子燒了
- Have a little faith, Dave. - Yes.
Dave.請相信我 好吧
Mayday!
救我
- What was that? - Don't stress him out.
怎麼了 不要告訴他
- Oh, that was... Aunt Jackie. - Yeah, she's making us a tasty five-course meal.
噢...是Jackie. .是，她給我們做了5道美味的食物
Really? Can I talk to her?
真的？我能和她聊聊嗎
She's practising her pole dancing.
她去練習鋼管舞了
Pole dancing? But, what happened with making dinner. Guys, what's going on?
鋼管舞 但是，那誰做的晚餐?到底怎麼了？
- Gotta go, Dave. - Alvin, I'm not kidding!
Dave.我得掛了 - Alvin我不是開玩笑的
- Get better! - Alviiiiiiiiinnn!!!
快點好喲 - Alviiiiiiiiinnn!!!
Yep, nobody does that better than him.
沒人比他做得更好了
Toby, Toby wake up.
Toby,.醒醒
- Sorry. - No, that's okay. What is it?
- 不好意思 - 沒事，怎麼了
- I had a nightmare. - Oh, the nightmares.I hate the nightmares.
- 我做噩夢了 -.噩夢，我最討厭做惡夢了
What was it?
夢到什麼了
I dreamt that we didn't have a family anymore.
我夢到我們不再有家庭了
Theodore, that couldn't happen.  No, you guys are tight.
Theodore, 那不可能的 不會的，你太緊張了
Nothing could ever separate you.
沒人會把我們分開
Less like an eagle swooped down from the sky like caw-caaaw!
就算老鷹來了也不能
Which couldn't happen ever. Why would you think that ever happened, you know...
這從沒有發生過 為什麼你認為會發生這樣的事呢？你知道....
The Eagles are in Philadelphia.
老鷹在費城
Sweet dreams.
好夢
- Toby, make it stop. - What are you doing?
- Toby,讓它停下來 你在幹嘛
There is something wrong with the clock. It won't shut up.
這鍾有點毛病 關不掉了
I can't sleep.
這樣我沒發睡覺
That's the point. It's an alarm clock.
那是因為它是個鬧鐘
It helps you wake up early in the morning.
它能讓你們早起
Why anyone wanna wake up early?
為什麼會有人想要早起？
For the school, you got to be there by eight.
去上學啊，你8點要到那裡
- In tðÞe morning? - Look, I don't like any others early anything more than you do.
早上？ 聽著，我可不想像你一樣早起
But we are in this together, Alvin. Soon you get to school, soon I get to compound and get back to sleep.
Alvin.但這是我們的事情 你越早到學校，我就能越早回來睡覺
- You mean you don't stayin' with us in school? - No, no , no.
你意思是說你不和我們一起呆在學校？ 是的
I've done my time making very much.
我學習造句的日子已經過去了
- But school is fun, right? - Fun? Well, i guess Maybe, it's... fun-ish..
不過學校很有趣，是吧? 有趣？我想是吧？
Hey, it's my cat!
嘿，那是我的貓
Hey kiddy it's me, remember?
嘿 小傢伙 是我 記得嗎
I treated you good.
我對你很好的啊
There, here we go.
我們到了
Enjoy your first day in school. See you around three-ish.
第一天上學玩得開心點 3點左右再來接你們
We got it. This got to be a walk in the park.
知道了，就像在公園一樣
I'm frightening.
我害怕
Hi, I'm Theodore.
嗨，我是Theodore
- Eagle. - Go eagle!
老鷹 老鷹來了
That wasn't very fun-ish.
這可不怎麼好玩
You must be our new students. I'm Dr Rubin, the principal.
你一定就是新來的了 我是Rubin博士，這裡的校長
And we are the Chipmunks.
我們是花鼠
Yeah, that will explain the fur and booshy tales.
是的，我能從你們的外表上看出來
- Follow me, gentlemen. - Gentlemen?
跟我來，男士們 男士們？
Oh, us. Right.
我們？好的
There was a minute left and we were down by two ...
還有一分鐘的時候 我們還落後兩分....
And I mind couch: I don't care if my leg is broken, put me in, I can win this...
當時我在想：就算我腿斷了也不要緊 讓我上，我一定能贏...
I never get tired of that story.
我從沒有放棄過
So I hobbled out barely able to stand...
所以我自己幾乎不能站立...
Did I mention my leg was broken?
我有提到我的腿斷了嗎？
- Mrs. Ortega? - Yes?
-Ortega女士? -是的
- Good luck. - Thanks.
祝你好運 謝謝
- Well guys, welcome to home room. - Good to be here, I hope.
男孩們，歡迎來到我們班 我希望你在這裡過得快樂
So this is a classroom?
這個就是教室嗎
I love the smell of zit cream in the morning.
我喜歡在早上聞奶油的味道
Hello ladies.
你好，小姐們
Hi, I'm Theodore. Hi, I'm Theodore.
嗨，我是Theodore
Yes, he's Theodore in case you missed it.
他是Theodore...假如你沒聽見
And I am Simon.
我是Simon..
My name Seville, Alvin Seville.
我是Alvin Seville
Enchant¨¦e... mademoiselle.
迷人的小姐
Somebody's have to knock these guys down to size.
找人量一下他們的身高才行
That should be pretty easy, really. They are only eight inches tall.
那十分很簡單 他們最多只有8英吋高
I had 15 cars. I mean that's like five more cars than anybody really needs.
我有15輛車 有超過5輛都是眾多人喜歡的
I had seven maids. Courtside seats to the Lakers.
我雇了7個女工 擁有湖人隊的場邊座位
Even my maids had courstside seats to the Lakers.
甚至我的女僕們都坐在那兒
Now, look at me.
看著我
Look at me. I lost everything.
看我 我失去了所有
Except for my dignity, they can't take that away from me.
除了我的尊嚴 .他們拿不走
And it's all because of them.
.而這一切都是因為他們
Oh, hey ...crackers.
咦，有餅乾
Now run around, hoping and praying that I could find other animals that can ...
現在奔波著 只是祈禱能找到其他會
sing or dance.
唱歌跳舞的小動物
Wait a second, you don't sing, do you?
等等，你不會唱歌？是嗎?
Hey, hey that's my muffin. Give me my muffin! You dirty rat.
嘿，這是我的鬆餅 給我拿回來，你這該死的小老鼠
I will get you Chimpmunks.
我會抓到你們的
Girls, we have to get out of here.
女孩們，我們得走了
I can't see.
我看不到
- My nose. - That's my tail! - Sorry.
.我的鼻子 那是我的尾巴，不好意思
- Move your ass. - Ok. Stop pushing me.
挪一下你的屁股 .好，別推我
- We made it. - Jets Records! - Phew!
我們成功了 唷
Oh, my gosh. It's him! Ian Hawke!
噢，我的天啊，是他 Ian Hawke
Mr Hawke?
Hawke先生?
That voice! I can't get it out of my head!
那個聲音，我能分辨出來
Hello, Mr Hawke?
Mr Hawke?你好
That not in my head, that's really happening.
好像不是做夢，是真的叫我
- What do you want? - We want to introduce ourselves.
你想幹嘛 我想自我介紹一下
That's right. I'm Brittany. And this is my sister Eleanor.
是的 我是Brittany，這是我的姐妹Eleanor
Hello, sir. Such a pleasure to meet you!
先生，很高興見到你
And I'm their sister Jeanette.  Although I feel more like an Olivia or sometimes....
我是她們的姐妹 Jeanette 儘管有時我感覺起來像Olivia..
Anyway, we are the Chipmunk girls.
不管怎麼樣，我們是花鼠美眉
We will be just so honored to have you to represent us.
我們很榮幸在你面前介紹我們自己
You made Alvin and the Chipmunk stars.
你讓Alvin花鼠們成為大明星
We wanna be stars too, yeah!
我們也想成為明星
And hangin' out with the Chipmunks.
和花鼠們一起玩耍
Ok, now listen before we get all girly and giggly about this, just tell me one thing ...
好了 在我們得到這些之前，告訴我一件事
You can sing, right?
你們會唱歌嗎？
Hang on, not here.
停，不是這裡
Why not we take this meeting upstairs in my penthouse office?
為什麼不到我的閣樓辦公室去開會
This is so exciting.
這太激動了
Oh, my gosh, can you believe it?
噢，天啊，真令人不敢相信
My first penthouse office!
我的第一個頂層辦公室
Oh, my... the Hollywood sign!
噢..好萊塢標誌耶
I thought you might like the view!
我想你會喜歡這裡的風景的
Ladies, tell me little something about yourselves.
女士們，告訴我一些關於你們的事
We grew up in a small town, population 300 and ...
我們在一個 只有300人的小鎮裡長大的
Really? That's fascinating. Great!
真的？那太棒了
All right, impress me!
好了 現在好好表現吧
One, two, three.
一.二.三
Girls, girls, girls.
女孩們，女孩們，
Guess who just became the number one Chipmunks' band in whole dang world?
猜一下誰會成為了全世界第一的花鼠組合？
Ian Hawke.
Ian Hawke.
So, when can we meet the Chipmunks?
什麼時候我們可以和花鼠們見面
That's an excellent question  and the excellent answer is...
好問題 答案是...
I don't really represent Alvin and the Chipmunks anymore.
我已經不再代表Alvin和花鼠們了
- Oh, no. Wha-what happened? - Oh, classic tale.
噢，怎麼回事？ 很老套的故事
Sweet and innocent when I met them, they had nothing ...and then I work my butt of
當我見他們的時候很可愛，天真 他們什麼也沒有，之後
to make them rock stars and...
.我盡了全力讓他們成為了搖滾明星
They changed. Turned out to be like bad cheese.
後來他們變了 變成壞蛋
- No. - That's terrible.
.不 多可怕啊
I know. I mean, I treated Alvin like my own son, you know.
我一直把Alvin當成我自己的兒子一樣對待
And he just goes and spits on me.
而他們就這樣離我而去
Literally. He filled his chipmunk's cheeks with saliva and just had at it.
實際上，我有的只是他們留給我的一臉口水
- Don't even get me started about Simon. - But not Theodore, right?
可別讓我提起Simon了 幸好不是Theodore
It's the cuddly ones you have to watch for.
這可愛的還更需要注意
But why we are talkin' about them for, c'mon? They are over, fired, nobledeuðÞe (noble death)...
為什麼我們要談他們呢 他們已經完蛋了，被解雇了..
Chipmunks' stupid sayin'.
花鼠們的蠢說法
But ...
.不過...
Girl Chipmunks' stupid sayin' ... Fasten your seat belts!
笨女鼠們，請繫好安全帶
So I eyed Jay Z's eyes right, and I said:  Jay, where is Beyonce?
我看著的他眼睛說，Jay，Beyonce在哪裡？
And he says : She's holding a plate  full of cheese balls, turn around ...
然後他說：她正拿著一碟子的 奶酪球...，我一轉身
And guess what..
猜是什麼
- She was. - PS, Dave left me in charge.
還真是她 Dave讓我看著他們
We stay up to ten every night.
我們每天晚上會呆到10點
Look what I can do.
.看看我能做些什麼
You're Theadorable.
你真是Theadorable
- I am so sorry. - That's cool. No harm done.
不好意思 沒事，沒有傷到我
Not yet. Girls, please, private conference.
還沒完 女孩們，我想和他們私聊下
Thank you.
謝謝
Listen up, rock stars.
聽著，搖滾明星
If you talk to those girls again you're dead.
如果你們再敢和那些女孩子聊天 你們就死定了
If you look at those girls again you're dead.
如果你們再看那些女孩子一眼 你們就死定了
If you even think about those girls...
如果你們再敢想想那些女孩兒.....
- Are you thinking about them? - Well, I am now.
你有想她們嗎？ 有啊，我現在想著她們
- That's it. - You are dead!
好 你完蛋了
Get them, c'mon! Crack you, you dirty rats!
抓住他，砸死你，該死的
Scatter!
散開
- That way. Over there! - I'm runin'.
那邊，這邊 我在跑
Hey Dumbo, catch me if you can.
嘿，笨蛋 有本事就來抓我
- You are dead! - Not!
你死定了 沒有
It's stretching time!
加時吧
Oh, boy.
天啊
Eagle.
老鷹
- Eagle! Eagle! - Get him.
老鷹，老鷹 抓住他
- Move! Move! - This way.
快！快！ 這邊
- Gotcha. - Wait, wait, come up...
.抓到你了 .等等..出來
- It's swirley time. - C'mon, c'mon guys, this is not so...
.漩渦來了 C'mon 這可不太......
Please, please!
求你了，求你了
- That's a good look for you! - Thank you.
有讓你好看的 謝謝
- I can't swim. Help. - Grab on Simon!
我不會游泳 幫幫我 抓住Simon
You okay?
還好嗎？
Well, uh, considering that you just saved me  from drowning in a toilet...
恩，還好，你剛剛把我從馬桶裡救了出來
I'm, uh, pretty good.
我嘛，很好
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
Alvin, Alvin!  We're not gonna solve anything with violence!
Alvin, Alvin!  我們不要用暴力解決
- It's the fatty ratty. - Cut it out!
這是條肥老鼠 閉嘴
- This rat has serious junk in the trunk. - Yeah, little fatty.
這老鼠一定在1D7D67A5里堆了很多垃圾 是啊，那麼多脂肪
Simon, does this make my butt look smaller?
Simon這樣會不會讓我的臀部看起來小一點
Theodore, your butt looks fine. Those guys are just some jerks.
你的臀部看起來很好了 那些小子只是一群笨蛋
You threatened to climb inside of him and build a nest.
你威脅他們說要在他們體內建巢？
That was out of line and not even sure that is physically impossible.
有點過分了而且甚至事實上也不太可能
- I should suspend all three of you. - Please do.
我應該將你們三個停職 可以
Instead I have the better idea.
我還有更好的主意
Due to budget cutbacks , we are in jeopardy of loosing our beloved music program.
由於預算的削減 我們的音樂規劃可能會受到影響
- That's awful. - I know.
太可怕了 我知道
But, there is one small ray of hope.
但是，我還是有一個小小的希望
Every year the District sponsors a music competition...
這裡每年都會舉辦一個音樂比賽
And the winner school receives 25,000 dolars.
.贏家將會得到25，000美金
IðÞ we win, we can save our program.
如果我們贏了，我們便可以拯救我們的音樂計劃
And you want us to perform?
你想我們去表演
I begin to think that you are a fan?
我在想你到底是不是我們的歌迷了呢
Why don't you sleep on it.
你們可以考慮一下
- Wait. - Great.
等等 好極了
Promise me that you won't say anything.
答應我什麼也不要說出去
The principal has a certain image to uphold. If Mr Fencle ever finds out about this ta...
校長一定會贊成的 如果讓Mr Fencle發現了可...
I just can't believe this, that you are actually sitting in my office. I have all of your CDs.
我真是不敢相信你們就坐在我的辦公室裡 我有你們全部的CD唱片
I even went to see you last year in Denver. That's where I got this.
我甚至到丹佛去看過你們 所以我有這個
It was my birthday. And I was like...Oh, the Chipmunks!
那是我的生日 但是我就像.... 花鼠們
So, what you say?  Will you represent our school?
所以，如何？ 你們會代表我們學校出演嗎
Honestly suspension sounds pretty good to me.
實話說，聽起來挺不錯的
Come on Alvin? One for all, and three for one.
Alvin? 一個對所有，還是3對一
Well put, Theodore.Very well put. Count us in.
Theodore 精闢，非常精闢 把我們算上
Go Eagles!
飛吧老鷹
Eagles? Where?
老鷹，在哪裡？
Ah, the penthouse limo.
閣樓轎車
Tr¨¨s exclusivo.
真獨特
Hey, isn't that that Chihuahua? Ya know, from the movie?
那個不是Chihuahua嗎 電影上那個
Uh, yeah, yeah. I mean, of course it is. Yeah, a lot of big names live here.
嗯，是，當然是他 很多大牌住在這裡
- Oh. Como esta? - I must have his autograph!
- Oh. Como esta? 我一要他的簽名
Whoa, whoa, Brittany. You wanna be a star, act like a star.
噢 噢 Brittany 你想成為明星，想要表現得像個明星
- You don't get autographs, you give 'em. - Oh, right.
你不需要他們的簽名，而是你簽名給他們 噢，好的
Hey, look over there, there's a couple of the Jonas Brothers.
嘿，看那邊，Jonas兄弟
- Where? I don't see them. - Here we are.
在哪裡？我看不到 到了
Ok, let's scootin' to my apartment ...
快去我房間
What? Did I... Oh, darn it! Darn it to heck!
噢，該死的
- What? What's wrong? - Girls, I apologise but ...
什麼？怎麼了？ 女孩們，真不好意思..
I seem to left my keys back in my office.
我好像把鑰匙留在辦公室了
What if one of you shroud through that mail slot and open it up for me from the inside?
你們其中一個能鑽進去從裡面把門打開嗎
I'll do it.
我來
I'm stuck.
我卡住了
All right, I got you, I got you!
好，我幫你，我幫你
Not so hard.
不會很難啊
I wanna lay off the nuts.
不要你來了
All right, how about you, glasses?  You are in better shape. Wanna go?
好，你來試下，眼鏡？ 你身材比較好，還是你去吧
- Well I'm not that good in things like this. - I got it!
.我不太擅長做這個... 我來
Impressive!
漂亮
Gee, Willakers!
哇奧.
Great. Bingo! This is the best treehouse ever!
好極了，瞧，有史以來最好的樹屋子
A red piano.
紅色的鋼琴
- Is this a dream? - Stand by and catch me.
我們是在做夢嗎？ 跟我來
- It's much better than a tree! - I just adore a penthouse view!
這比樹屋強得多了啊 我喜歡這裡的景色
Nice one, Hawke.
不錯 Hawke
- You like it? - Sure, Ian.
喜歡嗎 當然
- I live here. - It's so beautiful.
我住在這裡 這裡太漂亮了
The last time we visited Meerkat Manor ...
上一次我們來狐?莊園的時候....
Arrival group called the Commanders ...
有個來的團叫指揮官的....
was making large indoors in to the Whiskers' teritory.
在Whiskers弄了個大型的室內活動
Toby, I thought i was messy,  but this is really disgusting.
Toby, 這太雜亂了 真噁心
I feel like livin' in a dumpster.
感覺就像生活在垃圾堆一樣
Simon, it's Meerkat Manor on it. Watch with me.
Simon這是狐?莊園，過來一起看
You're right. I thik I'll relax, feelin' my nerves little bit...
你說對了 我是神經過敏了點
What is this?
這是什麼
You got to be joking? A taco.
一定是在開玩笑，玉米卷?
In a blanket? Toby!
竟然在毯子裡面Toby!
Ladies and gentlemen, goin' for his turkey is the Tobster.
先生女士們 Tobster 準備發球
Come on baby.
.加油
No problem. Watch and learn, my friends.
容易得很 我，學著點，朋友們
Oops, broken TV, I think this is the time to play my second favorite game.
哎呀，電視壞了，我想時候玩我的第二喜愛的遊戲了
Hide the broken TV from Dave. You wanna play?
把爛電視藏起來 你想玩嗎？
- No!!! - Go easy on him, Taco Boy.
不 對他別那麼嚴厲
This day has been bad enough already.
今天已經夠糟糕的了
Oh, I think I see what's going on.
噢噢，我知道怎麼回事了
- You guys are having some problems at school. - No, not really ...
你們幾個傢伙在學校惹事了是不？ 不，不是的
Unless you consider, having your head  dumped in public toilet, a problem ...
除非你認為 被扔下馬桶去也是個問題的話...
Squirrelees are the worst.
那麼糟糕
At least, that's what I heard.
至少，我聽到是這樣的
Because, there is no way that I possibly know that, on a personal level.
因為，靠我自己不可能知道這些
Toby, what was school like for you?
Toby,你覺得學校怎麼樣
- Toby? Tobyyy!!! - What?
- Toby? Tobyyy!!! 什麼？
What was school like for me? In a word?
覺得學校怎麼樣？一個詞？
Awesome! But, you know that 'cause I was like ...
棒極了 你知道 那是因為我太
Extremely popular.
受歡迎了
- Is that why you are still live with your grandmother? - And refer to yourself as Tobster?
這就是你和你奶奶一塊住的原因了吧 已Tobster自居？
And go peeoo-peeoo-peeoo all day?
就只會整天嗶..嗶..嗶
Bed time.
該睡覺了
Alvin! Alvin wake up and turn off the alarm.
Alvin! Alvin醒醒，把鬧鐘關掉
Alvin, I'm not kidding. I'm not kidding, buddy, turn it off!
Alvin 我沒開玩笑 沒開玩笑 快關掉它
Guys, guys ...
夥計們
Boys, this isn't funny.
小伙子們 這可不好笑
Hello? I need help.
你好，我需要你的幫助
A man got us. He wants to take us to eternal place.
有個人抓住了我們 他想帶我們去個地方
- School. - Howgh!  - Have a heart.
上學 發發慈悲吧
Have a heart. Dave wants you to school, so you are goin'.
發發慈悲吧 Dave想讓你們去上學 你們就去吧
Don't worry about taking us three, Toby. We gonna be all right.
Toby.不要擔心我們三個 我們會很好的
- If it hurts? - Guys, come on.
如果很糟糕呢？ 夥計們 快點
Trust me, the second day is never as bad as the first.
相信我，第二天一定比第一天要好
Glasses! Glasses!  You wouldn't hit a guy with glasses, would y...
眼鏡，眼鏡 你不會用眼睛打人的 對吧
Right in the pancreas.
直搗黃龍
Nurse?
護士？
C'mon, Alvin! Remember the five D's! Dodge, duck, dip, dive, and dodge!
C'mon Alvin! 記住5個字，閃，趴，蹲，沖，跑
You're next, furball.
你就是下一個 毛球
You talkin' to me? You talkin' to me?
你和我說話嗎？
I'm the only one here, so you must be talkin' to me.
這邊只有我一個了，你一定是在跟我說話對吧
- Did you see that? - Hallelujah!
你看到了嗎 哈利路亞！
Unbelievable, he caught it. You're out, man.
.真不敢相信，他接住了 你出局了
And the tackle made, she got's in.
成功接到了
- He got hands. - I think that's paws actually.
他接得到 我想是個觸地
We can definitely use him on the team.
我們球隊需要他
Hey, furball, how would you like a spot inðÞthe football team?
嘿，小東西 你想加入足球隊嗎
- Football? Moi? - I got to say you're good.
足球隊？ 你身手不錯
I'm gonna let you hangin' out with us at lunch.
我希望你和我們一起去吃個午飯
That is, if you wanna be on the team?
就是說，如果你想成為我們其中一員的話
- Interesting proposition. - Alvin?
不錯的建議 - Alvin?
- Maybe I'll get back to you on that. - This is a one-time offer.
我考慮好再回復你 只有一次機會
Don't take too long and think it over .
不要想太久
Great, but I will dish my brothers!
好極了，但是我要先搞定我的兄弟們
Just to become the first chipmunk ever to  play an actual pose on a football team.
我要成為花鼠歷史上的第一個球員
No chance.
沒有機會了
The stadium is unanimous.
球場是公平的
It stots and goes, it's out, it's out... and he catches it!
出局，出局，他接到了
The crowd goes crazy.
觀眾們瘋狂了
Me?
我
I think that super cool jock table is paging you.
我想那個超級冷酷的人在叫你
Why would I go over there?
為什麼我要去？
Look, if I really need to worry about being popular.
聽著，我還擔心太受歡迎呢
Hello, talking Chipmunk. World-famous rock star ...
你好 會說話的花鼠 世界知名搖滾明星
Dive with his own flesh doll. Guys, I'm on pajamas.
夥計們 我還穿這睡衣呢
Not to toot my own horn bike.
老是自吹
Come on, it's delectable.
拜託，這是件愉快的事
- Just go, Alvin. - Really? You really mean it?
Alvin.去吧 真的？
- Yeah. - Thanks. I'll be right back.
是的 謝謝 我很快回來
- What's up, geeks? - What's up, man?
有什麼事 怎麼了
Bring it.
說吧
I got it, I got it I...
.我能行
Not.
不
- I think he's cute. - Me too.
我覺得他很可愛 我也覺
Toss.
我拋了
Call me.
打給我
I'm tellin' you, Chipmunks are old news. I got the next big thing.
告訴你，花鼠們已經過時了 我又有新的了
Singing female Chipmunks.
會唱歌的女花鼠們
God, what part of singing female chipmunks some of this people do not understand...
為什麼女花鼠就得不到他們的肯定
Girls, we are goin' to school.
女孩們，我們也去學校
He's up, and he scores.
他會上 而且會得分
Hey, right up, ass? Wow, don't hate on a high five?
嘿，我接到了，為什麼不給我來個擊掌
Yeah, high five.
好
Look Alvin, I know you've guys been busy with your sporting gathers and what not...
聽著，Alvin，我知道你一直在忙你的球隊
- But I can really use your help at home. - Oh, no can do.
但我確實需要你回家幫幫我 我無能為力
Ryan is gonna teach me how  to get pretty girls to do my homework.
Ryan將教我怎麼找個漂亮女孩子來幫我做作業
Alvin, you promised Theodore we hang out.
Alvin，你答應過Theodore我們會出去約會的
We are watching Meerkat Manor tonight. No pretty girls.
今晚一起看狐?莊園 沒有漂亮女孩
- Dude, I can't swing it today. - That's what you say every day, Alvin.
我今天沒有空 你每天都這麼說 Alvin
Not to remind you it's your day to do the laundry.
不要再要我提醒今天輪到你洗衣服
Better listen to your daddy, Alvin. You don't wanna get grounded?
最好你聽爸爸的話 Alvin 你可不想被關禁閉
- Are you going to pick that up? - Are you going to make me?
你要去撿起來嗎 你想逼我嗎
Au contraire, mon fr¨¨re! I'm just going to elegantly show you how it's done.
好， 那讓我來教教你怎麼撿起來
My brother, he's a real jokester. Always do.
他是一個愛開玩笑的人 經常這樣
I'll see you guys around.
再見
- That's my play. - That's my play.
輪到我了 輪到我了
Why are you tryin' to embarrass me in front of my friends?
為什麼你總是想在我朋友面前讓我難堪
Are you kidding me? They are the ones which should be embarrassed by.
你開什麼玩笑 他們才是應該感到難堪的人
- Good luck with the show, guys. - First row seats. Can't wait!
比賽加油 等不及了 第一排的位置
So, which song are we gonna sing?
我們將會唱哪一首歌？
No pressure, but the whole school is counting on us.
沒壓力 不過學校就靠我們了
Oh, relax! It's like Ryan said:  Who's gonna beat singing chipmunks?
放心，就像Ryan說的：有誰能夠打敗會唱歌的花鼠們？
Finally. Oh, Simon is dreamy.
不管怎樣，Simon是個做白日夢的
- I think Theodore was looking at me! - Yeah, I know.
我覺得Theodore好像在看著我 對 我知道
But guys remember what Ian said? We can't trust them.
你們還記得Ian說過什麼了嗎 我們不能相信他
- What happened? - I never thought I'd say this but...
怎麼回事？ 我本來不想說的，但是..
- Pink is my new favourite colour. - Her glasses were quite fetching.
粉紅色是我最新喜歡的顏色 她的眼鏡很迷人
She's like a beautiful green gumdrop.
她就像是個迷人綠乳糖
If you guys want to do this you got to pay attention.
如果你們想幹好 就要集中注意了
- Maybe, this is a good time for us to take a break. - Good call,take five.
也許，現在是我們休息一下的好時候 恩，好的，5分鐘
She's right. We need to focus.
她是對的 我們要集中注意力
This is for my screen saver.
這是為了我的屏幕保護
- Hey buzz! - Hey guys? Are you guys ready to go?
嘿 Buzz 嘿 夥計們 準備好了嗎
'Cause I've got a lot of important staff  to do at home.
我在家還有很重要的事要做
- You must be their guardian? - God, that I am. Yes I am.
你一定是他們的監護人了？ .天啊，是的，我是
Hi. How are you, Dr Rubin? I know that because I went to school here a few years ago.
你好Dr,Rubin ， 我以前也在這學校念過書
I don't know if you remember me, Toby Seville probably not...
不知道你是否還記得我 Toby應該是不記得了
Toby? No way? Hi! Hey, no braces.
Toby？嗨，是你，沒有帶牙套了？
- I think it's great. - I did ...
好看多了 我把..
I did get the braces off,'cause they were just...
.我把牙套解了，因為...
I know a guy who actually works on drum heads. I'll be in the car, guys.
我認識一個男孩子也是打鼓的 孩子們，我在車上等你們
Somebody is in love.
有人愛上誰了
We are going to replace everything. Chipmunks' honor.
我們將替代所有的東西 花鼠們的地位
The old false modestly suck up routine.
The old false modestly suck up routine.
- I thought I smelled a rat. - May I help you Mr Hawke?
我想我聞到了花鼠的味道 Hawke先生 有什麼可以幫到你..
I was wondering if I could help you, Ijust heard about your musical competition ...
我在想也許我能幫助你們 我剛剛聽說了你們的音樂比賽
and I just get down here as quickly as I could                                                                         to volunteer my girls.
我就盡快到這裡來推薦我的孩子們
That's very thoughtful of you, but I've already made up my mind.
謝謝你的周到 不過我已經做了決定了
Perhaps this will change your mind.
也許這會讓你改變決定的
Girls.
女孩們
They are with Ian?
她們和Ian在一起？
One, two, one, two ...
一二，一二
They're astounding.
她們太棒了
Good people of West Eastman, you have  just witnessed the debut...
朋友們，你們剛剛看的是女鼠們
Of the Chipettes!
的首次亮相...
Thank you!
謝謝
- Well? - They were splendid. But as I said before...
怎麼樣？ 她們太了不起了，但就像我以前說的
I have made my decision.
我已經下了決定了
I see. You've made your decision.
我知道了 你已經做決定了
I don't need to speak out of school doctor,  but in the true spirit of democracy ...
我不需要說服一個學校老師 真正意義上的民主
which our great wonderful country was founded upon...
是我們偉大國家的根基
I say, lðÞt the people vote.
我想說，讓人們投票決定吧
Let them choose. One person, one vote, I say, let us vote!
讓他們來選擇 一人之投一票，讓他們決定
Let us vote.
.投票
let them sing.
讓她們唱
You make a persuasive case, Mr Hawke.
你很有說服力， Hawke先生
All right, here is what I'm going to do.
好，這就是我將要做的
This friday, each group will perform one song in front of the student body.
本週五，每隊將在學生面前表演一首歌
Whoever gets the most applause, well, will represent the school.
誰獲得最多掌聲，那麼 誰就代表我們學校
What?
什麼？
Thank you. We made it.
謝謝，我們成功了
Oh, it is on, like Donkey Kong!
我們像大型金剛一樣強
The Meerkats huddle together, at the end of a dramatic day ...
狐蒙聚在一起結束了戲劇性的一天
to reaffirm their family bond.
重申了他們的家族觀念
The whiskers are going to have to rely on each other more than ever.
Whiskers將比以往更加依賴彼此
Guys, I'm so happy that Mrs Ortega can rehearsal with us every day after school.
夥計們，真開心每天放學後 Ortega女士 能幫我們排練
- Wow! Every day? - Stop right there, ok!
啊？每一天？ 停一下
We are the team, we need you.
我們是一個團隊，我們需要你
Would you relax? We are not going to lose.
你可以放鬆點嗎？我們是不會輸的
We'll talk about this in the morning.
我們明天早上再談這個
Not much to talk about. I will see you at the rehearsal.
沒什麼好談的 .那排練上見
- Stop huggin'. - I am not huggin'.
別抱了 -我沒有抱
You might as well be really obstacles  in the face countryside because you are in fact huggin'.
你或許也想成為真正的障礙面朝那邊，因為你確實在抱
- I'm not. - I saw, and saw...
我沒有 我看到了 而且....
I think I will sleep in my own bed tonight.
今晚我睡我自己的床
You know for me, I'm so glad I'm not a meerkat.
你知道我的，我很高興我不是蒙狐
- Oh, really? And why is that? - I would never hug with you!
噢，是嗎？那是為什麼呢？ 我就不用和你擁抱了
Toby, can I sleep with you?
Toby，我可以和你一起睡嗎
- What? - Be kind to me.
什麼 對我溫柔點
My brothers are fighting.
我兄弟在吵架
What? Geeeee... ok.
什麼？ 恩，好的
Man, Dutch Oven!
啊，烤箱？
Not the Dutch Oven! Anything but the Dutch Oven! I can¡¯t breath!
別是烤箱啊 除了烤箱都行，我不能呼吸了
It's to late! It burns! It burns!
太晚了 燒起來了 燒起來了
Now, let's see. What else am I in the mood for?
噢，我來看看，我還有心情做什麼
How about a side order of friendly advice, courtesy of me?
聽下我意見怎麼樣
No, thanks.
不，謝謝
Grapes, please.
Grapes,等下
Heh, heh. Excuse me. Ahem.  So, uh, well, I, I, I just wanted to warn you... about Ian.
不好意思 Ahem 我是...想讓你警惕一下Ian
What?
什麼？
You should be grateful to him.  He did everything for you, Alvin, and you broke his heart.
你應該感謝他 他做的一切都是為了你，而Alvin你卻傷了他的心
Hmm,really. How do I put this gently!
噢 真的嗎 那我怎麼做得更大度一點
He's the devil,  he doesn't have a heart,
他是個壞人 他沒心沒肺的
and one of the things he did for us  was put us in a cage!
比如說他就曾把我們關在籠子裡
- Oh, Alvin, he would never do that. - Yeah, guess, you were there, I forgot...
Alvin，他不可能做這個 是，想想 你曾在那兒，我忘了.....
- You, you'd better watch out. - I don't need any advice from you.
.你最好小心一點 我不需要你的任何建議
-But... -But, nothing, Alvin! Ian's taking us straight to the tooooooopppp!
不過.. 不過，沒什麼，Alvin，Ian會讓我們成為大明星
Right, straight to the top. I got it.
好，成為大明星，我知道了
Yeah, funny. Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
是，真有趣
Hah, hah we are, so, going to destroy those Chipmunks!
哈哈哈，我們就要把花鼠們擊退
- I don't want to destroy them. - Me neither. I just want to hang out with them.
我不想把他們毀了 我也是，我想和他們一起出去
All right, look. If you feel that way ...
好吧 如果你們這麼想......
- Maybe we should just withdraw from the contest. - What?!
也許我們應該退出比賽 什麼？
I'll put you all in Fedex package and mail you back to whatever tree you came from.
我會把你們用聯邦快遞寄回你們來的地方的
Sounds good? Ok then. Take room from the top. Let's go!
聽起來不錯吧？，好 開始
Wow, wow stop. Short one in a green dress...
嘿嘿，停 穿綠色衣服的矮子.....
- what's your name again? - Eleanor.
你叫什麼名字？ - Eleanor.
Yeah, look. I'm losin' you there, you know. Have you always been that short?
好吧 我都看不見你了 你一向來是很矮的是吧？
- I guess. - You've got to work on that.
我想是的 那應該做點什麼？
Ok, all right. Let me try somethin' here.
好的，那我試試這個
Brittany, here. Come up here. No, you two stay back.
Brittany過來，過來這裡 不，你們兩個退後點
A little further.
再遠一點
Oh, yeah! Now that I like!
噢 好，現在可以了
It's not just because Brittany is more  than mega-ultra superstar than you guys.
因為 Brittany比你們兩更像 超級巨星
Good, good. Ok, you know what, let's get a  little more separation. Brittany, stay there.
很好，很好， 再分開一點點。Brittany,你呆在那兒
Get a little more separation from you guys.  Give her some room! Give her some room, guys.
再和她們分開點 給她一點空間，孩子們
All right. Watch me now.
好了，看著我
One, two, three ... Watch me. Watch me now.
一，二，三 看著我
- Hello? - Toby?
你好 - Toby?
What are you doing in the house? Where is Aunt Jacky?
你在房子裡幹什麼？  Jacky阿姨在哪裡？
Dave, hey Dave, what's happenin'?
Dave 嘿 Dave 發生什麼事了
Aunt Jacky is in the hospital.
Jacky阿姨在醫院
I am a little worried. Who's watcin' the boys?
我有點擔心 誰照看孩子們啊？
I am.
我
- So, Dave, how is Paris? - Wait, are the boys behaving?
Dave 巴黎怎麼樣啊？ 等等，孩子們還乖嗎
Absolutely. They've been just pitchy.
當然很好，這裡還是天黑呢
- Toby, what's going on? - Nothing. Don't even worry about it.
Toby,到底怎了啊？ 沒事，別擔心
You know, I know that you're not suppose to be stress down.
你知道嗎，我知道你壓力太大了
-So I'm gonna go right now, but it's all good here. Come home soon. Bye. - Toby? Toby?
我現在要走了，這邊一切都好 再見 - Toby? Toby?
Nurse, get me out of here!
護士，把我弄出去
Help...
救命啊
I don't mean to interrupt your game but I saw you stand up to Ryan when he littered...
我不是有意要打斷你玩遊戲 只是我看到你和Ryan站在了一起當他混亂的時候
- That's to guts. - Really?
那是需要勇氣的 真的？
That's the kind of guy we are looking for. Jeremy Smith, Student body president.
我們就是尋找這種人 我是Jeremy Smith，學生會的主席
- How do you do, I am ... - International recording star ...
你好 國際巨星
- And litter monitor Simon Seville. - Litter monitor?
還有垃圾管理員 Simon 垃圾管理員？
Litter monitor,  it's a new position that we've created,
垃圾管理員 這是我們創造的新職位
to help raise awareness to the presssing problem  in our society.
去幫助和提高同學們 環保意識
I agree 99% plus 1.
我百分之99同意再加1
You did the math.
你會算術
Simon, I know this is a lot to ask...
Simon,我知道這是一個很難的請求
We are lookin' for a take-charge guy who take charge of this very rewarding position.
我們在找一個有責任心的人來擔任這個好職位
What do you say?
怎麼樣？
Excuse me, everybody. Quick announcement. ðÞ597
.打擾一下各位 我有個通知
I'm Simon, I am the Litter monitor. Put your trash in a garbage can. He's out.
我是 Simon,新的垃圾管理員 請把你們的垃圾都扔到垃圾桶裡
Hello, ladies. You are probably unaware that you've thrown a racker on the ground, so ...
.嗨，小姐們 你還沒有意識到你的垃圾 已經掉在地板上了吧？...
We gonna just call this morning warning.
我們應該管這個叫早晨警告
Carry on.
繼續
- Right up, dudes? - What up, pal!
好了嗎 兄弟們 幹嘛
Hey, everybody! Check it out. The newest member of the football team.
嘿，大家看看 這是我們球隊的新成員
- Soon enough for his first away game. - Guys, don't mess with me.
很快就有他的第一場比賽了 夥計們 別惹我
I talked to couch. You are in.
.我和教練說了 .你加入了
- That's great. Awesome. - So, check it out, hey man...
太好了 看看
We are watchin' the new litter monitor.
我們新的垃圾管理員
I even wasn't aware that school even had a litter monitor.
我還不知道學校有垃圾管理員
It don't but don't tell him that.
別告訴他
- Are you goin' to pick it up? - No.
你打算撿起來嗎 不
Well, I'm sorry to hear that,  I guess I'm going to have to, anyway a tuition.
很遺憾聽到你說這個 我想我應該記你的罰款
No, I got a suition from littery.
不，垃圾的罰款？
Oh, you wanna play that game, do you? Guess what, I can play that game all day long. - Simon!
噢 你想跟我玩？ 猜怎麼著，我成天都玩這個 - Simon!
It's a joke, dude.
開開玩笑的
Litter is no joking matter.
但是垃圾不是笑話
You're the joke. We are messing with you.
你是個笑話 取笑你的
There is no such a thing as Litter monitor.
這根本就沒有什麼垃圾管理員
What? Big liar, huh!
什麼 大騙子
You knew about this, Alvin? Spelling "brother" mean anything to you?
Alvin，你早就知道了？ 兄弟對你來說是什麼意思
Yes, of course.
當然
Well, yes he has some new brothers now he is on football team.
他先在有新的弟兄了 他進球隊了
You still hadn't pick up that litter.
你還沒有撿起那垃圾
Want me to get rid of litter?
你叫我去撿垃圾？
- Let's start with you. - Hey, let go, let go. Noooo!!
就從你開始 放手，放手
Touch down.
觸地特分
I'll catch with you guys in a second.
我等一下再去找你們
Ok, I'm a total jerk, I admit.
好，我承認我是個笨蛋
So are we cool now?
我們沒事了吧
Ok, I'm going to put this behind us ...
好吧 已經過去了
- For Theodore's sake. - I know.
為了Theodore 好
That's why I'm giving you my...
那是我為什麼要給你我的.....
The Alvin currency that I will be on that stage Friday night.
Alvin的資金
Wait, wait, wait!  Why woudn't you be there?
等等 為什麼你不去？
Because I had a...
因為我有...
- What? - I...
什麼？ 我
- You have a what? - A socker ball game. Now I said it.
你有什麼 .一場球賽 我終於說了
A football game.
足球比賽
- Simon, Alvin is everything alrigt? - Theodore. Hello!
Simon，Alvin還好吧？ - Theodore. 嗨
Yes, we are fine. Just a little dumpster wrestling.
我們很好 我們在玩摔跤而已
- It's crazy in here. - Right.
真是瘋了這裡 是的
Don't worry Theo, everything is gonna be fine.
不要擔心，Theo 一切都會很好
- Alvin, do not miss that Sing all. - Don't worry, Simon.
- Alvin,別錯過演唱比賽 不要擔心Simon
I'll be there. I can prove.
我一定會去的，我保證
Hey guys, thanks so much for helping out today.
非常感謝你們今天的幫忙
"Toys for Tots" is a really cool organization. So, everybody is gettin' cool points today.
"Toys for Tots"是一個不錯的組織 今天大家辛苦了
- What's goin' with Theodore? - I have no idðÞa.
Theodore怎麼啦？ 我也不知道
- Hey Eleanor, why don't you see if Theodore needs some help? - Ok.
嘿 Eleanor 你去看看Theodore需要什麼幫助嗎 - 好
- They don't look very comfortable. - My shoes?
它們看起來不是那麼舒服 我鞋子嗎？
- They are not. - But Ian says that I need to work on being higher.
確實不舒服 但是Ian說我要嘗試變得高一點
Well... I think you look great just the way you are.
你本來看起來就已經很好了
You do?
你這麼想？
Hi, you've reached Dave Seville, please leave a message.
嗨，我是Dave Seville 請留言
Hi, Toby. This is Julie Ortega, we talked yesterday...
嗨, Toby. 我是Julie Ortega，昨天和你說過的一些的
a sort of it. Anyway, the reason I'm calling,
我打電話是想告訴你
is that I am worried about Theodore, he's been acting a little down lately.
我有點擔心Theodore 他情緒有點低落最近
I hope you are going to the "Sing All" Friday.
我希望你回去週五的「sing all」
You know in his down,  Theodore needs all the support he can get.
你知道Theodore 需要所有他能得到的幫助
So, I'll see you there. I hope we get a chance to talk. Bye.
.比賽那天見 希望有機會和你聊聊 再見
Ok, folks. Time to get behind your Warriors...
好了 弟兄們 該你們勇士上場了
They are listening Eagles down by five,  with only thirty seconds left on the game.
老鷹隊落後5分 比賽還剩下30秒
- Time is running out for the ... - ...He really needs to make a move here or...
比賽時間不多了 他需要想想辦法了
This game is over. - I know, put me in.
比賽結束了 我知道 讓我上
Hey, put me in.
嘿，讓我上
- Time out, Time out. Time out Eagles
暫停，暫停 老鷹隊請求暫停
Number 15 got nine seconds to make it to the game.
15號只有9秒的時間贏得比賽了
All right boys, it's time for the big A.
好的，該是雄起的時候了
I'm going to crush them and burn them to pain. The Alvinator is in the house.
我要踢到他們頭破血流
Are you sure about this?
你確定？
Four to ten say that we need to go for the secret weapon.
.我們該使出我們的秘密武器了
Chip is right. He left decision on me.
他說的對 他讓我來做決定了
Time to make history, boys.
.創造歷史吧
I'm taking you down, Jennifer.
我來擊敗你 Jennifer
You are the one going down, rat face.
是你要失敗 老熟臉
I'm going to crack you like an acorn  and eat you for dinner.
我要把你像橘子一樣吃掉再
With some fava beans and a nice chianti.
加點蠶豆和紅酒
Is this something about my father?
這是關於我老爸嗎
One, two ...
..一二
I'm comin'!
我來了
That's what I'm talkin' about. Don't hate the pain, hate the game.
這才是我說的 要恨就恨這場比賽吧
I love the hunt, man.
我愛這場打獵 兄弟
Final score: Eagles 15. The Warriors 14
最後得分，老鷹隊15，戰士隊14
What you think about that, sucker?
怎麼樣？傻B
- That's what I'm talking about. - You're really muscle chipmunk.
這就是我想要的 你們可真是強力鼠
Give me a A, give me an O, give me a W, give me an E, give me a M...
給我A給我O給我W給我E給我M
How that spell...awesome.
怎麼說來的..太棒了
I am the king of the world.
我是國王
Party with Alvin.
我Alvin一起玩去吧
Everybody to the beach house.
都到海景房去
Let's do it.
走吧
Look guys,  I just want you to know that I'm here for you.
我來這裡是為了你們
There is plenty of time.I'm gonna go find Alvin. Everything is gonna work out.
有的是時間 我去找Alvin 所有的事都會解決的
-Thank you, Toby. Ladies and gentlemen, Dr Rubin
謝謝你Toby 女士們先生們，有請Dr Rubin
Thank you, students.Thank you.
謝謝 學生們 謝謝你們
Between the Chipmunks and the Chipettes.
就在花鼠和女花鼠們之間的比賽
Remember students, there are no winners or losers.
不過記住 這裡沒有贏者輸者
Remind me to tell the Chipmunks that one, when we blow up off the stage.
當我們贏得比賽 記得提醒我通知花鼠們
...To our school, a chance to win 25 000 dollars to save our music department.
有機會作為學校代表贏取25000美金拯救我們的音樂系
So, without further due, I give you ... the Chipettes.
接下來， 請上我們的女花鼠們
This is it girls, can you believe it.
該我們了 美女們 難以置信
Brittany, your time to shine baby.
Brittany, 展現自己的機會到了
- Go up there and knock them dead. - Yes sir, I can do it.
去好好秀給他們瞧瞧 是 我能做到
- You two I just wanna let you know, not to get in Brittany's way. - Ah, ok.
你們兩個 我只想讓你們知道 別擋Brittany的路 好的
You like what you see, call Ian Hawke ...
喜歡你所看到嗎 給Ian打電話
310-555-5309.
310-555-5309.
Don't worry, Simon, Alvin will walk through that door any minute now. Alvin!
別擔心 Alvin很快就回來 Alvin！
I'm back.
我回來了
- Thank you so much. Thank you. - Well done, ladies.
謝謝 唱得好，女孩們
And now, let teared for the group that will rock you like a hurricane.
讓我們來拭目像暴風雨一樣的花鼠們
At least that is what many of you students have told me.
至少就像很多你的學生告訴我的一樣
Here they are...the Chipmunks.
歡迎花鼠們
Hey, you know they say there is no "I" in the word "team", and they are right.
嘿 你知道嗎 有句話說在團隊裡沒有自我 他們是對的
But,you know where is "IN" ? Alvin.
你知道IN是什麼嗎？Alvin
Such to be you.  Girls!
就是像你們 女孩們
Sadly, he's correct.
可悲，他是對的
- Did you find him? - Guys, sorry, I searched the whole perimeter.
找到他了嗎 .對不起，我找遍了周圍都沒有找到
And I don't know why, but the team is not back yet.
我也不知道為什麼 整個隊也沒有回來
What should we do?
我們怎麼辦
I would ...
我應該....
I would ask someone...who's not me.
我應該叫別人.....但不是我
I know what we should do.
.我知道我們應該怎麼做
Hi, everyone.
嗨，大家好
Our brother, Alvin couldn't be here today.
我兄弟，Alvin今天來不了了
Thing is, we never performed without Alvin ..
重要的是，我們不會出演的如果Alvin不在
and we are not starting now.
我們還沒有準備好
You can't have two little pigs, you can't have only two musketeers so...
你們不能只有兩頭小豬 你們不能只有兩個士兵 所以.....
You know you can't have only two chipmunks.
只有我們倆不能唱
Thank you.
謝謝
I'll take you home.
我帶你們回家
You hear that, girls?
女孩們，聽到了嗎
That...is the sound of success.
勝利的聲音
I relize how devastated you...
.我知道你們的失望
Chipmunks' funs must be...
但是花鼠們也一定有自己的原因
So I guess that means that the Chipettes...
所以我想這意味著女花鼠贏了..
Come on girls, let's take a victory lap.
過來，女孩們
Hey, come on guys, let's go.
過來
Britt, we have to.
Britt,我們得去
Let's go.
走
Thank you.
謝謝
Life is good.
生活真美好
Especially when you're not a loser.
尤其你不是一個失敗者的時候
Hey guys? I'm here.
嘿 夥計們 我在這兒
Guys?
兄弟們？
Oh, great.
噢 太棒了
They are gone, Alvin.
Alvin.他們走了.
- They never gonna forgive me. - You know ... Alvin...
他們永遠也不會原諒我的 你知道嗎 Alvin...
Ian waðÞ right. You don't care about anyone except yourself.
Ian他是對的 你永遠也不會關心其他人除了你自己
And oh, by the way,  I never wanna to win this way.
噢，順便說下 我也不想以這種方式贏你
Simon, are you awake?
Simon,你醒了嗎
Theodore, I don't blame you for being mad.
Theodore,我不責怪你生氣
I ran away from home?
我離家出走了？
Don't look for me in the Zoo, because I'm not there.
別去公園找我 我不在那裡
Oh, no Theodore ...
不.不 Theodore
Hello?
你好？
Meerkat family?
狐?家族
Is anyone home?
有人在家嗎
My name is Theodore, I like to be in your family.
我是Theodore，我想成為你們的一員
Maybe they are hiding.
也許他們藏起來了
Don't be afraid.
別害怕
You are not a meerkat!
你不是狐?
Toby, you take the lions, the tigers and the bears ...
Toby你來找老虎，獅子和熊那邊
Simon and I will take the butterfly room.
Simon和我去檢查蜜蜂那邊
Nice Eagle.
好老鷹
Don't move Theodore.
不要動Theodore
No problem there.
好的
Hang in there, hang little guy. We'll get you out from there.
別動 別動小子 我們馬上把你就救出去
Ok, we need a plan.  And we need carefuly executed plan.
我們要定個計劃 我們需要定個精密的計劃
Or you can just ride in there like a maniac.
或者你可以像個瘋子一樣跑進去
Theo, watch out.
Theo,.小心
Hi, I'm Theodore ...
嗨，我是Theodore
Hey birdy, look up in here, are you hungry? Catch this "A"?
嘿，大鳥，看這裡，你餓了嗎 先抓這A
That's for appetizer.
那是開胃菜
Let's all just relax, and we talk this out, ok!
放鬆點 我們出去聊好嗎
Look, I guess why you want Theodore, I do,
聽著 我想我知道你為什麼想要Theodore 真的
but I'm sorry, I can't let that happen.
不過 不好意思 我不會允許這事發生的
He's my brother.
因為他是我的兄弟
Not let him know that, because I've been a such a big jerk lately.
別讓他知道 因為最近我真的是個大混蛋
If anyone deserves to be eaten, it's me.
如果誰是值得被吃掉，那就是我
Not really.
不是真的
I got you, Alvin.
Alvin.我來幫你
Watch to the eagle.
當心老鷹
Their only mortal enemy is a piggy elephant. Luckily I speak a little habitat.
他們的敵人就是大象 幸好我知道它們在哪裡
I think it's working.
我想這行得通
Guys, that was huge.
天啊，這太大了
He's right.Now we are one for all and three for one?
那我們現在是一對所有還是三對一
Come on, Simon, hug it out.
算了吧，擁抱一下
You know I'm sorry, Sy.
你知道的，對不起
Sy, don't make me up to kiss you because  I'll do it.
不要叫我去親你我可是會的
I don't care.
我不介意
Here come the lips! The makeout train leaving the station.
過來 終於好了
I think after all, I'll take that hug.
最後 我想我想要那個擁抱
Justine, call Ian Hawke.
打Ian Hawke電話
310-555-5309.
310-555-5309.
Morris, get me that Ian Hawke on the phone.
Morris,讓Ian聽電話
There you are.
你們在這裡
My sweet little money makers.
我親愛的掙錢小東西
Do you remember when I told you that I would make you all big stars?
記得我曾經和你們說過 我會讓你們變成大明星
Well, guess who's opening up for Britney Spears at Staples Center tonight?
猜猜是誰在斯台普斯中心 為Britney設了場？
Am I dreamin'? oh, my gosh!
我在做夢嗎 天啊
Oh, wait, we can't.  We'll miss the school concert!
. 等一下，我們不能去 我們不能錯過學校的音樂會
That's correct. You will miss the school contest.
是的 你們會錯過學校的音樂會
It was never about that stupid school contest, it was always about making Brittany a star.
其實根本就不是為了學校的競賽 其實一直都只是為了把Brittany弄成明星
That's what you wanted, right?
這就是你想要的是嗎
- well...yes. - Tonight is your big chance.
恩，是的 .今晚是一個很好的機會
It's all about you, Brittany.
Brittany.全部都是為了你
But what about Jeanette and Eleanor?
那Jeanette和Eleanor呢
They can sing backups, I got them some staff too.
她們可以助唱 我也會給她們薪水的
- We are her sisters. - We either sing together or not at all!
我們可是好姐妹 要麼一起唱要麼不唱
Ok, fine. All I ever needed is the B-girl.
好 我需要的只是Brittany
Ian, I won't do it without them.
Ian 如果她們不去我也不去
Ok, fine, fine. Let's move on to Plan B.
好吧，好吧，那就實行B計劃
Ok, who likes barbecue?
誰喜歡燒烤？
Because I know this awesome little barbecue restaurant in the valley,  that makes the best roasted chipmunks.
我知道有一間非常好的燒烤餐廳 花鼠烤肉做得很棒
Real tasty. Unless of course, you wanna sing?
味道好極了 當然，除非你們唱歌
Welcome to West Eastman, and thank you for supporting music in our schools.
歡迎您的到來.. 和謝謝你們對我們學校音樂的支持
Now remember,the group you pick tonight, will win 25000 dollars for their school.
記住，獲勝的那一組將會為他們 學校贏得25000美金
Now there's got a lot of acts, and we have to  trow heat off by nine-thirdy so ..
現在我們有很多的表演 我們需要在9點半的時候結束
without no further due, representing Orange girl put your hands together for...Lou Rosarro.
不用多說，舉起雙手歡迎我們的橘子女孩兒.....Lou Rosarro
We meet again. You wanna a piece of it?
我們會再見嗎 你也想要分一杯羹嗎
Eagle.
老鷹
Ian Hawke?
Ian Hawke?
I'll take that.
我來
I didn't realise that you are runnin' a low life.
我還沒有意識到你現在處於下層社會了
- Alvin, - Brittany? - Aren't you guys still interest?
- Alvin, - Brittany? 你們對表演還有興趣嗎
I'm not gonna be able to perform tonight.
我今晚不能去表演了
What about the music department? The whole school is counting on you.
那我們的音樂系怎麼辦？ 學校全靠你們了
I know, I know. I had to listen to you about Ian.
我知道 但是我不得不聽你說關於Ian的
Don't tell me...
別告訴我...
Yes, he locked us in a cage.
.是的，他把我們鎖在籠子裡
This is this the biggest you have? I have a licence to call and asked for the biggest thing, that's not the biggest what you got.
這就是你們最棒的了嗎 我可有權利要求你們使出你們最好的 這可不是你們最好的
I will go and take the news to Dr Rubin.
我會把這消息告訴Dr Rubin
- Brittany? - Alvin, don't move.
- Brittany? - Alvin,別動
You got it. Brittany, I'm comin' to get you.
收到 Brittany 我來了
Simon, how do you know to hit a lock?
Simon,你知道怎麼打鎖嗎？
Roger that.
收到
I need to get to those girls. Fast.
我要快點救那些女孩出來
I know how.
我知道
The third number is notoriously the hardest to crack ...
.第三個號碼是最難解的..
I'm assuming that provide number that we can't assume...
.我只能提供號碼，其他的我不會...
The first two numbers are one. I got to go with one.
.前兩個號碼是1 我相信是1了
It opened.
打開了
- All right,  girls ... - Ian is coming.
太好了 Ian來了
Put the phone back, hurry!
盡快打給我
Get ready to be fabulous.
準備好表演
We are ready.
我們準備好了
Yeah, you're better be. Because tonight's performance it's gonna put me back on the top.
你們最好給我準備好 今晚的表演我要拿回我原來擁有的一切
And now please welcome...Cherisse.
下面我們歡迎cherisse
Driver man, take me to the ArðÞna. The VIP entrance.
司機，帶我去Arena 貴賓入口
Tout de suite. A little moonroofs actions.
.盡快 Moonroofs的表演了
Moonroofs are go, moonroofs, roofs, roofs...
Moonroofs上了, moonroofs, roofs, roofs...
Champagne.
香檳
If you don't mind ... If I do...
.不介意我喝點吧 .如果我喝了
You know why I don't mind if I do? Because tonight we've got to toast ...
知道我為什麼要喝嗎？ 因為今晚我們就要舉杯慶祝
To a very special someone, named me.
一個特別的人，就是我
They said I couldn't do it,  they said I never bounce back.
他們說我不可能做到 他們說我永遠不能死魚翻身
Guess what? Time to kiss my ass.
猜猜怎麼樣 .見鬼去吧
A toast! To the ladies who gonna make the world forget about the Chipmu...
乾杯，讓全世界把花鼠忘掉
No, no, no, no! What are doin'? Alvin.
不，你們在幹嘛？Alvin
Hi Ian! Good to see you. You look alright!
嗨 Ian 很高興見到你，看起來不錯
No, no! I signed a contract.
不，我們已經簽了合同的
- Jump, Jeanette. -Wait! - I'm not really good...
Jeanette跳，等等 - 我不是太好...
I bet it you don't perform.
我打賭你一定沒得表演了
- Gas, Alvin. - You got it!
猜猜Alvin. 你成功了
Hey, Ian! In the words of McDonald, you're fired!
Ian，用麥當勞的話說，你被解雇了
- Hey guys, any sayin' about Alvin yet? - No Alvin and no Chipettes.
Alvin有說是什麼嗎？ 沒有Alvin就沒有花鼠女孩
Just Dr Rubin and the entire school are counting on us.
校長和學校都靠我們了
Well, you know...you know don't worry everything will work out...ish.
別擔心 一切都會好的
- Faster Alvin! - Don't worry...
Alvin!快點 別擔心
I'm gonna get a real help from my friend, stay there.
我現在去找我朋友幫忙 等在這兒
Roger that Alvin.
知道了 Alvin.
Just like I'm back on the racetrack.
就像我回到了賽場上一樣
Where you going? What are you doing?
你去哪兒 想幹嘛
Wait 'til I tell everybody back home that I've saved Alvin Seville.
等回家後我告訴所有人我救了 Alvin Seville
I think I owe you an apology about Ian.
我想我還欠你一個Ian的道歉
Stick with me Britt. I'll never stay alive.
和Britt在一起 我死定了
Oh yeah , I'll never got to do that.
是嗎 我真的不該這麼做
I got to say, he's definitely persistant.
我得說 他真的很堅持
- We got to lose him. - Hang on.
我們得趕緊把他甩掉 坐好了
I got a plan, jump on a count of three!
我數3一起跳上去
- Oh, that's it. - I didn't like heights.
就這樣 我畏高
- Keep your tight Jeanette. - Bring my girls right to me.
Jeanette.抓緊了 帶女孩來我這裡
- We need a  remote. - Guys, I know what have to do.
我們需要那遙控器 夥計們 我知道應該做什麼
Hats off on Ian.
脫下Ian的帽子
The remote.
遙控器
I can't reach it.
我拿不到
I'm doing it. Hold my ankles.
我在努力 抓住我的腿
I got it.
成功了
I got it?
我成功了？
- Well done, Jen. - Top work, Jeanette.
做得好 Jeanette.
Hey Ian, you were wrong. I don't need these.
Ian, 你大錯特錯，我們不需要那些
- Bye bye. - Adios, Ian.
再見了  再見 Ian
And now, for our final act of the night...
現在，請出我們最後的表演者
And, listen we have last second change to the line up, but we don't think you gonna be to disapointed.
聽著，還有一秒改變局面 相信你們一定不會失望的
Representing West Eastman it's...the Chipmunks.
West Eastman的代表--花鼠
We may have to go up there , Theodore.
Theodore.看來我們得上去了
If there are no Chipmunks we gonna have to move on.
沒有花鼠們 我們還得繼續
I don't wanna be good again.
我不想再做好人了
I'm sorry, but we haðÞe to move on.
抱歉了，我們得繼續下去
I'm not a Chipmunk, as you can see.
你們知道我不是花鼠
Where is the music you loser? Where is the music? Music?!
音樂在哪兒 失敗者 音樂在哪裡？音樂..
Ok, I got to song.
好，我唱
Well, that...was huge.
哇，強！
Thank you.
謝謝
The Chipmunks are in the building.
花鼠在這裡
- It is the Chipettes! - Alvin.
那是花鼠女孩兒 - Alvin.
Hello, West Eastman.
你好， West Eastman.
I'm puttin' her down. Hang on.
我們下來了 站穩了
- Alvin. - Give me the high-five, brothers.
- Alvin. 給我擊掌 兄弟
Ladies and gentlemen, representing West Eastman  it is my great pleasure...
女士們先生們West Eastman的代表
This is such an honor.
真榮幸
- For you or for us? - For us.
你還是我們 我們
We get it! Come up, guys.
一起來
And now I give you the Chipettes and the Chipmunks.
讓我帶給你們花鼠女孩兒和花鼠
Thank you.
謝謝
Hey everybody, it's clear that we have a winner of the 25000 dollars ...
是誰奪得25000美金相信大家已見分曉
And it's West Eastman High.
就是West Eastman
Guys, we did it.
我們成功了
It's all yours, Dr Rubin.
這是你的 Dr Rubin.
Ladies and Gentlemen, The Staples Center is proud to welcome the Chipettes.
女士們先生們， 斯台普斯中心非常榮幸歡迎女花鼠們 921
Hi everyone, I'm Jeanette and I am Eleanor.
嗨，大家好，我是Jeanette，我是Eleanor
And I'm Brittany.
我是Brittany.
And we are the Chipettes.
我們是女花鼠
One, two, three.
一二三
- Dave, you are dancing. - You are even good, Dave. Yeah!
- Dave,你在跳舞 你好了，太好了
- Welcome home. - So, did you miss us?
歡迎回來 想我們嗎？
Of course I missed you. You are my boys.
我當然想念你們 你們是我的孩子
Ok Dave, just did how much you miss us. There are now six of us.
Dave,你有多想我們? 現在我們是6個了
Alvin, what did you say?
Alvin, 你說什麼
The Chipettes need a place to cresche , right?
女花鼠也需要一個地方住的，是吧？
So I said that you said, they can stay with us for as long as they needed to.
所以我說像你說的 她們想和我們在一起多久都行
Ok, this works for Dave. Everybody shake what your mama gave ya!
好， 大家動起來
Look at you. All ready for bed.
看看你 準備睡覺去
Looks like the Chipettes had a good influence.
看看女花鼠們給你多好影響
Thanks, Dave.
謝謝Dave
Ok guys now lights out.
好，我現在要關燈了
Good night everybody.
各位晚安
- Alvin? - I'm not tired.
- Alvin? 我不困
Sorry, but you've got school tomorrow.
不行，你明天還要去學校
Not tired.
不困
Alvin, come on. It's time for bed.
Alvin,快點，該睡覺了
Still not tired. More light.
.還不睏，不要關燈
Tired. Just kidding. Much more light.
不是開玩笑的 不要關燈
Alvin, that's it! Don't make me come over there...
Alvin,夠了  不要讓我過去...
Oh boy, I finally got relly, really tired.
噢.我終於真的累了
Good night, Dave.
晚安 Dave.
Alviiiiiiiiinnn!!!
Alviiiiiiiiinnn!!!